caraca moleque
Charlie Brown
he's coming invading the city
this one is the founding PC of Zé's brownie
my partner
and today he came here to Santos to have a look
not that we are getting ready
the possibilities that we can do
up brother
hit here we
over
I want the brand to depend on an influencer
if the guy doesn't know my story
just stops in stock
from this campaign here then
15 if I play 2
2 I have 1 motivation out of 30
disaster you called from the time
fucking
of the time
found me
fucking
papo challenge hand
for me it's excellent
if I meter 500 brownie today daily
without what a mess
so bora is
but that's it brother
I think it's
the way
the series is about to end
then
really has to gas it now and show the stop
the idea I don't know what
and then we step on the opportunity
also to be able to make the noise
that's where the money is
pear then be careful this is a bike path
oh there is a bike path
turned on
10 am
continues
I'm with the bailiff
if you can play just a little bit here
you're understanding what i'm telling you
understood
take the pencil to say the idea valeu
o ali o
I've already looked there already
here original code
Charlie Brown already
oh where's the rest bro already
sold in the afternoon
the brand is taking shape brother
it's cool
head towards Marcilio street days
here O tent here O
save someone in the house
of course
we know him who sent a message
followed him
born weeks ago
I'm seeing it and I believe he was in
Santos and the idea we are going to get is this
bro and here ended the video ended
haha